So I'm sure I'm pressing
Oh, ain't you sick from above?
You know you make my world light up
When I was young, when I was hurt
It came to live me home
Love is a dream and loves a truck
Oh, no, I think I'm gonna speed my eyes up
When I was a river, try up
It came to rain and fly
This is a dream for me, dream for me
When I was so nervous, I'm all on a scene for me
No, I just can't get it alone
I just can't get it alone
I choose a reason for me
When I was so nervous, I'm all on a scene for me
I'm feeling drunk and I'm so high
So high, so high
Oh, I'm feeling drunk and I'm so high
Oh, no, I think I'm gonna speed my eyes up
I ain't you sick from above?
I feel your colds in through my blood
Love is a dream and your love's about to make the stars come out
It's wings on me, wings on me
When I was so heavy, I'm all on a scene for me
When I was so nervous, I'm all on a scene for me
Oh, I'm feeling drunk and I'm so high
souls
dramatic
I'm a sure I'm Christ